A Finding Aid to the Frank Stella Papers, 1941-1993, bulk 1978-1989, in the Archives of American Art AAA.stelfran
Archives of American Art
- Financial Records, 1972-1986; Series 7; (Boxes 8 - 12 4.0 linear feet)
  - Paid Bills, 1972-1986; 7.2
    - Tompkins Tooling Industries, Inc. (10-A1-II), 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - TOR-TWE, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 2x Construction Co., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - U-Z, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Payroll, 1986; 7.3
    - Frank Stella Main, Frank Stella Special, Delahanty Stock Farm Inc., and Stock Blue Realty Corp. Payrolls, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Payroll Taxes, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Petty Cash, 1984-1986; 7.4
    - Receipts, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 15-25)
  - Race Horses, 1983-1985; 7.5
    - Bonita Farms, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Brasil Stable, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Breezy Hill Farm, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Breffni Stud, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Bridlewood Farm, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Camac, R.W., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Clermont Farms Ltd., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Delahanty (see also: Stock Green Farm), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Homeplace, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Magenta Stables, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Nancy E. Dennis Racing Stables, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nuench, Felix, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Sanchez, Juan, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Schmitt, William F., D.V.M., 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Stock Green Farm (see also: Delahanty), 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Track Account, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Printed Matter, 1957-1993, undated; Series 8; (Boxes 12-13 and ov 14; 1.5 linear feet)
  This series is organized into seven subseries:
  8.1: By Frank Stella, 1984-1989
  8.2: Announcements of Limited Edition Prints, 1979-1993, undated
  8.3: Articles, 1957-1991, undated
  8.4: Exhibition Catalogs, Inviations and Announcements, 1960-1993, undated
  8.5: Events with Stella Partiicpation, 1982-1988, undated
  8.6: Miscellaneous Items, 1958-1993, undated
  8.7: Oversize, 1984-1992
  - By Frank Stella, 1984-1989; 8.1
    - "An Artist's View of Prints" in Books and Prints, Past and Future: Papers Presented at the Grolier Club Centennial Convocation, 26-28 April 1984 (photocopy) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - "Commentaire du tableau Complexité simple-Ambiguité" in Kandisky, Album de l'exposition, Centre Georges Pompidou, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Working Space: The Charles Eliot Norton Lectures 1983-84, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - "How Velázquez Seizes The Truth That Is Art," New York Times, October 1, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Announcements of Limited Edition Prints, 1979-1993, undated; 8.2
    - Gemini G.E.L., undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Petersburg Press, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Tyler Graphics, Ltd., 1975-1993 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Articles, 1957-1991, undated; 8.3
    - Feature Articles about Stella and his Work (includes interviews), 1957-1991, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Articles Briefly Mentioning Stella or Containing Reproductions of his Work, 1979-1989, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Reviews of Exhibitions, 1981-1990 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Reviews of Working Space; Advertisements and Notices, 1986-1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations and Announcements, 1960-1993, undated; 8.4
    - Solo Exhibitions, 1960-1988 (Box 12, Folder 28-33)
    - Solo Exhibitions, 1989-1993; undated (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Group Exhibitions, 1969-1992, undated (Box 13, Folder 3-6)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibitions with Stella on Jury or Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Events with Stella Participation, 1982-1988, undated; 8.5
    - New Jersey Center for Visual Arts Printmaking Symposium, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1958-1993, undated; 8.6
    - Auction Notices, 1984, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Awards Programs and Announcements, 1981-1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Information (photocopies), 1958-circa 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Brochures of Public and Corporate Collections, 1979, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Gallery Ads, 1982-1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to Political Fund Raising Events Hosted by Stella, 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Publicity, 1976-1992, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Norton Lectures, Harvard University, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Picture Postcards of Ronnie Peterson and Hans Joachim Stuck, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Poem, "To Frank Stella of Flin Flon VI, 1970" in The Surveyor's Hand by Anne Cherner (photocopy), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Reproductions (see also: Oversize), undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Oversize, 1983-1992; 8.7
    - Exhibition Posters; Posters Designed by Stella for Events and Causes; Reproduction of The Tail, 1984-1992 (Box 14 (ov))
- Photographs, 1941-1989, undated; Series 9; (Box 13; 0.25 linear feet)
  Photographs are of people, exhibitions, works of art by Stella, places, and miscellaneous subjects. See also the Princeton University papers (Series 2) which include two photographs of a painting executed by Stella during his student days.
  This series is organized into five subseries. Within each category, photographs are organized into the subjects indicated by the folder titles listed below. Each folder is arranged chronologically.
  9.1: People, 1941-1993, undated
  9.2: Exhibitions, 1982-1989
  9.3: Works of Art, undated
  9.4: Places, circa 1974
  9.5: Miscellaneous 1979-1986
  - People, 1941-1993, undated; 9.1
    - Frank Stella, 1941, 1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Frank Stella and Harriet McGurk in India; Frank Stella and Infant Son, 1977, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Frank and Harriet Stella with Jimmy Carter and Joan Mondale (inscribed by Carter), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Frank Stella with Students, Studio in a School Association, Inc., circa 1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Frank Stella with Japanese Hosts, 1991; Frank Stella in Korea, Delivering a Talk, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Frank Stella and Fishing Companions, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Others (Joan Mondale at home with loan collection of contemporary paintings, circa 1980; Stella's son; Gabriella Henkel), circa 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Exhibitions, 1984-1989; 9.2
    - Gallery Opening, Frank Stella: Neue Werke, Galerie Würthle, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Installation Views, Frank Stella: New Work, M. Knoedler & Co., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Works of Art, undated; 9.3
    - By Stella, 1983-1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - By Stella (35-mm color slides and color transparency), 1985, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Places, circa 1974; 9.4
    - Tyler Graphics Ltd. Studio, circa 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1986; 9.5
    - Horses; The Lawrence Realization, Noisy When Hot, Belmont Park, N.Y., 1979, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art Banner Mimicking a Black Painting by Stella, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 34)